- What's your favorite fruit?
- It, uh...
(Steph:)Strawberries.
(Sheldon:)Mm, technically not a fruit, but all right.
(Sheldon:)Where did you do
your medical internship?
(Steph:)Uh, Lawrence Memorial
in Galveston, Texas.
(Sheldon:)Really? That's where I was born.
- You're kidding.
SHELDON: No.
(Sheldon:)I spent so much of my childhood
at that hospital. It...
(Sheldon:)When I was 12,
I got to ride there in a helicopter.
- What? What happened?
- Radiation burns.
(Sheldon:)A little mishap
while I was building my own CAT scanner.
(Steph:)I'm sorry, you tried to build
your own CAT scanner?
(Sheldon:)No, I didn't try, I succeeded.
(Sheldon:)I was briefly able to see the inside
of my sister's guinea pig, Snowball...
(Sheldon:)...before he caught fire.
(Sheldon:)It led to an interesting expression
in our house:
(Sheldon:)Not a Snowball's chance
in a CAT scanner.
(Leonard:)Uh, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)Excuse me.
(Sheldon:)When I come back, just for fun,
the subject will be alternative history.